Guide to the David McDaniel and Richard Redlon Papers, 1980-1990
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
David McDaniel and Richard Redlon Papers
1980-1990
Redlon, Richard
McDaniel, David A.
0.5 cubic feet (2 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
The David McDaniel and Richard Redlon Papers consist cheifly of correspondence between the two men after graduation from Vassar College. Of particular interest is the description of gay life and culture in the 1980s, with some discussion of AIDS in the later letters.
Biographical Note
David A. McDaniel (VC 1979) and Richard O. Redlon Jr. (VC 1980) began their friendship while students at Vassar. McDaniel became associate librarian at the Bancroft Library, University of California, Berkeley. Redlon was an historic preservationist and an architecture critic for a Boston magazine. Both men died of AIDS, McDaniel in March 1990, Redlon in December 1993.
Scope and Content Note
The David McDaniel and Richard Redlon Papers consist cheifly of correspondence between the two men after graduation from Vassar College. Of particular interest is the description of gay life and culture in the 1980s, with some discussion of AIDS in the later letters.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Subject Headings
Subjects:
Gay men; AIDS (Disease); Gay culture--United States
VCL Categories
LGBTQ (Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual,Transgender & Queer) Life and Culture
Encoding Information
Finding aid encoded by Jason Kovari, 24 Feb 2009.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Eric Marcus, December 1998.
Container List
- Biography, collection notes and photographs (Folder 1.1)
- 1980 (Folder 1.2)
- 1981 (Folder 1.3)
- 1982 (Folder 1.4)
- Jan-May 1983 (Folder 1.5)
- Jun-Dec 1983 (Folder 1.6)
- 1984 (Folder 1.7)
- Jan-Jun 1985 (Folder 1.8)
- Jul-Dec 1985 (Folder 1.9)
- 1986 (Folder 2.1)
- 1987 (Folder 2.2)
- 1988 (Folder 2.3)
- 1989 (Folder 2.4)
- 1990 (Folder 2.5)
- undated (Folder 2.6)